Gar-chan,
ガーちゃん、
Just sit there for a while.
ちょっと そこに座ってみ
hand.
て
Flow away.
流 して
It's already this black.
もうこんな黒じゃん
Put it in your mouth.
口の中で入れちゃえ
I'll make it grow in your mouth.
口の中で大きくさせちゃう
It's a nice black color.
気持ちいい黒じゃん
You can move the skin.
スキン動かしていいよ
Let's take a look at your face.
顔見てみよう
It's cute, isn't it?
可愛いでしょ
Have you grown up?
大きくなった?
Shall I let you talk as you like?
好きに喋らせてみるか
mutual affection
そうし
Good morning.
よう
You can do whatever you want to that dick, so let's make it feel good.
その チンチン好きにしていいから気持ちよくしておこう
Kuro: You can't say that.
黒 じゃん、それ言っちゃダメです
Did you eat black rice?
黒じゃん食べたかな?
still.
まだ
I'm still holding back.
まだ我慢してる
It's black, I'm still holding back.
黒じゃん、まだ我慢してる
Chin-chin, you know it's getting hard?
チンチン、辛くなってんの分かる?
It's black, do you want to go now?
黒じゃん、もう行きたい?
Well then, hurry up and give me a break.
じゃあもう切ら早く、ちぼちぼして
Cut out the inside of the mouth.
口の中も切り出す
Show me.
見せろよ
I'll eat it with pie.
パイで食べるじゃん
I just took it out.
さっき出したばっか
There's not enough movement like that.
そんな動きが足りない